[lute playing]
[Jaskier]
♪ I'm weak, love, and I am wanting ♪
♪ If this is the path I must trudge ♪
♪ I'll welcome my sentence ♪
♪ Give to you my penance ♪
♪ Gorgeous garroter, jury and judge ♪
♪ Lovely garroter... ♪
♪ Gorgeous garro... ♪
Which one do you prefer?
"Lovely"? "Gorgeous"?
[horse snorts]
Is the whole metaphor landing,
or is it too cerebral?
- It's been an hour.
- [Jaskier] ♪ Gorgeous... ♪
Let's get on
before the beast gets hungry again.
- But we made a deal.
- We made a deal with a livin' witcher.
No sense in hangin' around
to pay a dead one.
[Jaskier] ♪ Gorgeous garro... ♪
- [man grunts]
- Bollocks! Oi! No. No, no, no! No!
Aah! You stop... stop that,
or I... I'll, uh...
Or you'll what?
Sing us to death?
Perhaps you did not hear the man.
[Jaskier] Yeah! Perhaps you didn't...
Di... Sorry, who are you?
Move along,
old man.
Do as the bard asks
or I'll be forced to draw my weapons.
What weapons?
I see no steel 'ere.
- Hm!
- [cries out]
- [yells]
- Oh! [exclaims]
Steel won't be necessary.
[Jaskier breathing heavily]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
I believe those are mine.
[Jaskier stammers]
Geralt, they... With the...
This woman just killed a man
with her bare hands
for trying to steal your horse.
Maybe she'll make
a better travel companion, then.
Uh, I'm sorry, who are you, exactly?
I am Borch Three Jackdaws.
These are my companions,
Téa and Véa.
I've been looking for you,
Geralt of Rivia.
This is a first for me,
and that's saying something.
I've very few firsts left.
But to dine with the Geralt of Rivia...
Your adventures are legend.
You're welcome.
Est Est, small.
I suppose you want me to tell you
why I've sought out
such an accomplished monster hunter.
- Don't trouble yourself on my account.
- [chuckling]
- [Geralt] I just want food.
- I knew I'd like you.
That was the first reason.
One of everything you have.
And keep the ale coming!
[innkeeper] On its way!
The second one is this.
A short while ago,
a green dragon landed across the border
in King Niedamir's mountains.
I know what you're thinking.
"Impossible, dragons are so rare."
But it's true.
Locals spotted it
and went after it in search of treasure.
Of course, they succeeded only
in wounding the creature
and angering it so righteously
that it swooped down from its lair
and set half a hillside ablaze.
- Hm.
- [Borch] Dead sheep everywhere.
You have the most incredible neck.
- [sighs]
- It's like a... a sexy goose.
Ugh.
Gu... guzzling.
[Borch] Now, the King is in a bind.
He's set to marry the princess
of his rival kingdom, Malleore,
which means it's bad timing
to have a murderous pest lurking about
in the mountains.
He's commissioned a hunt to kill it.
Four teams have signed on.
The winner gets the dragon treasure hoard
plus the title of lord
over one of his new vassal states.
That is... if he survives.
What does this have to do with me?
I want you to join my team.
[Jaskier] I can hear it now,
a tale of two Zerrikanians
and their valiant poet lover.
Oh! [chuckles]
We're so doing this. We're in.
You've wasted your breath, Borch.
I don't kill dragons.
[sighs]
[Geralt] Take my advice.
No treasure is worth dying for.
Depends on the treasure.
What I need is...
a new adventure.
One final first before I'm too old
to do anything but die.
You think killing a dragon
will bring you that?
All I know is there's one path
up the mountain,
and it's overrun with monsters.
With you on my team, dear Witcher,
we'll be unstoppable.
- [men laughing]
- [man] Someone get me a fuckin' drink!
- Barman!
- Those dwarfs will be part of the hunt.
Barman.
- Geralt could handle them in his sleep.
- Fuckin' right!
He said he wants four fuckin' pints!
- Now.
- Or maybe a little bit awake.
[Téa] Then there are the Reavers.
Have you heard of them, Witcher?
Yes.
And the answer is no.
You feel it just the same as me...
that hole inside you.
That itch that can't be scratched
that burns your brain,
keeps you awake at night.
Come with me.
I'll show you what you're missing.
What am I missing?
Sorry to interrupt this lovely moment...
That's only three.
Where's the... What's the fourth team?
- [Geralt] Hm.
- Them.
Oh! [laughs]
Ooh-hoo-hoo! Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Thank you so much. It's been very nice.
Thank you for the wine and the pies,
but as the man said,
we really can't get involved.
Geralt, shall we?
- I'm in.
- Mother of...
The hunt begins at sunrise.
[sighs]
Your man might've mentioned
that the road was too narrow for horses
in his initial sales pitch.
Welcome to the world, Jaskier.
Damn it to Korath!
What's got your goat?
Someone's stolen my pack.
Probably those fuckin' Reavers!
Aye, well...
three days' journey
and only one route to the top.
Leaves plenty of time
for me to piss in his gruel! [cackles]
Aah.
Name's Yarpen Zigrin.
Geralt of Rivia.
- And my name is Julian Alfred Pankratz...
- Aye. I know.
You'll fetch a goodly amount for that mare
if you sell now!
Charming how everyone wants to get
their hands on Roach these days, isn't it?
He means we won't make it out alive.
Wait, what? No one mentioned anything
about impending death!
How is it
that I've walked this earth for decades
without coming across a witcher,
and then the first one I meet,
I can't get rid of?
[Jaskier] I'd say
something strange was afoot,
but then again, witchers are bound
to bump into monsters eventually.
[laughs]
- Jaskier.
- [Jaskier] Yennefer.
The crow's feet are new.
Yeah, well, your jokes are...
old.
[scoffs]
[nickers]
Thanks, Roach.
- What are you doing here, Yen?
- [Yennefer] I'm here with my escort.
Noble Sir Eyck of Denesle.
To assist him in killing the dragon.
For kingdom and glory!
Till we meet again, Geralt.
See you, Roach.
[bugle blowing]
[bugle blowing continues]
[Ciri] Who is Geralt, exactly?
Did my grandmother know him well?
Why did she never mention him
to me before... that night?
Protecting you has always been
our primary purpose.
Why'd she let him claim
the Law of Surprise?
What's that even mean?
When one has saved another
from certain death,
the Law of Surprise can be claimed
to pay that debt.
[Ciri] Who did Geralt save?
[sighs] Your father.
Duny. In payment, he bound you to Geralt.
- It's your destiny.
- [scoffs]
Then why hasn't he found me yet?
Questions, questions.
You'll be together soon.
Exactly as your grandmother wished.
Make haste, children.
[Jaskier] It is so kind of you
to share the spoils of this expedition
with an old man such as Borch.
You're like two fiercely loyal...
uh, friends.
I wanna say friends. Relatives.
Contract security.
To hunt with him is an honor
unsullied by payment.
But why? [chuckles]
He is the most beautiful.
[sighs]
You worry if you blink,
you'll never see her again.
You're in love with her.
Or...
the danger here isn't the dragon.
[Borch] That's why I brought you along,
Geralt of Rivia.
Nothing scares you.
[Geralt] Huh.
Then you don't know
Yennefer of Vengerberg.
[Borch laughs]
May she be the worst encounter, then.
[Jaskier] Melitele preserve us.
What happened here?
[Geralt] Dragons avoid people.
It should have left when they attacked.
I don't get it. Why the retaliation?
When your species is
on the verge of collapse,
perhaps everything becomes more desperate.
[Jaskier] Yeah, I mean, you can use twigs,
uh, but I... I mean, I personally prefer...
using flowers, you know?
Roses.
Daffodils.
- [hissing]
- Flora and, yikes, fauna.
A cactus, if she's really into it.
Ladies, you look famished.
Allow me to wander aimlessly
into this thicket
and retrieve for you, uh...
a tasty afternoon treat.
Uh... uh...
Right. Hm.
- I am hungry. Anyone else hungry?
- [sighs]
I could genuinely eat a...
Okay.
- [grunts]
- [animal barks]
[whimpering]
There's something back here.
It sort of looks like a faun.
- Jaskier...
- [Jaskier] Hello.
- Hello, little fellow.
- [animal whimpering]
Aw! Aren't you just the cutest...
[animal growls]
[stammers] Most...
terrifying thing I've ever seen
in my entire life.
Right, run away! Run away! Geralt!
[animal growling]
It's one of your... friends again.
[exclaims]
[low growl]
- What in the name of Bloemenmagde is that?
- [Geralt] It's an hirikka.
It's probably starving.
Sheathe your weapons.
- [grunts]
- [roars]
[whimpers]
- [yells]
- [hirikka cries]
- [Eyck grunting]
- [slashing and thumping]
[yelling]
[continues yelling]
[panting]
- For kingdom and glory!
- Sir Eyck!
[sighs] Yeah...
You could have been killed!
If we'd fed it, it would've gone away.
Thanks.
That knight may be a fuckin' dumbbell,
but I'll be damned,
the dragon won't stand a chance.
[Borch] Um...
I'm not sure I'd eat that, good sir.
[scoffs]
Knights never waste a kill.
[coughs]
It's precisely why I'll make a great lord
to Niedamir's vassal state.
A great knight must lead by example.
- For...
- Kingdom and glory.
We know.
My subjects will be the luckiest serfs
in all the lands.
Especially with the beautiful Yennefer
as my mage.
I cannot wait to serve you, My Lord.
How would you like to serve me tonight...
- Witch?
- Careful, Boholt.
[grunts]
[chuckles]
So, the Witcher wants
to play knight too, hmm?
No.
She's plenty able
of murdering you herself.
[Boholt laughs]
What's so amusin',
you overgrown cock hair?
I'm just wondering who I will kill first.
The monster,
or the monster hunter.
Hm.
[Eyck's stomach gurgles]
[sighs]
Oh, dear.
Um... I'm afraid I must take my leave.
Lady Yennefer,
may I escort you to your tent?
Will you be joining me?
- Uh... My Lady, I would...
- [stomach gurgling]
...never degrade your honor
in such a way.
[snorts] I hate to break it to you,
but that ship has sailed,
wrecked and sunk to the bottom
of the ocean.
Ow.
- [farting]
- Oh...
[straining] I need a shit.
[laughs]
[Eyck whimpers]
[Yarpen] So, shall we tell
the poor bastard
that he's vying for a vassal state
that won't exist in a decade?
States rise and fall like the tide.
Nothing new.
This is fuckin' new!
The rightful son of Nilfgaard
has returned, burnin' through the south.
With Fringilla as his mage.
[laughs] Nilfgaard's a joke.
I saw it with my own eyes
down in Ebbing.
Those zealot freaks are inching closer
by the day.
Won't be long till they try
and take Sodden.
Next it'll be Temeria.
Redania.
- Cintra.
- No.
Queen Calanthe would die
before letting them take what's hers.
Perhaps if Nilfgaard's religious zeal
had been tempered earlier
by a stronger hand...
If you'll excuse me,
I must get my beauty sleep.
I don't think it'll make me prettier,
but I need sleep too.
So... we're all about to have
new evil overlords,
and dragons are, in fact, a thing.
- Good day all round.
- [laughing]
Oh, you've all seen
a dragon before, have you?
Geralt, will you please tell them?
Their numbers are dwindling.
Treasure seekers saw to that.
But they do exist.
What people call "green dragons,"
like the one we have here,
they're the most common.
Red dragons, less so.
Black dragons are the rarest.
Gold dragons are rarest.
Gold dragons are a myth.
For a gold dragon to exist,
it would... have to be the result of...
an accidental, unique mutation.
And in my experience,
mutations, they're intentional.
But it doesn't matter.
Mutant or myth,
gold dragons met the same fate
as anything too different to endure.
They died out.
There are other ways of enduring.
If it's legacy you're after,
perhaps you should take the overgrown
cock hair's advice and become a knight.
[laughing]
Sir Witcher...
the White-Haired...
of Rivia.
[chuckling]
You'd make a rather shitty one,
refusing to slay dragons.
[laughing]
But probably not as shitty a one
as Sir Eyck of Denesle!
[laughing]
[Mousesack] Keep walking.
The Nilfgaardians could be anywhere.
We're not safe yet.
[Dara] How did you escape the attack,
Mousesack?
[Ciri] Dara, please.
[Dara]
Ciri says you vanished into thin air.
Why did you abandon your Princess?
We were...
I was pulled through a portal
by Nilfgaard,
kidnapped and held prisoner for days.
And how did you escape them?
Geralt.
He sent me to get Ciri.
The Witcher?
Trained to fight and bound to Ciri.
And he rescued you
so you could then rescue her?
- Alone?
- Ask him yourself.
He's in a town
just past this thicket of trees.
We must find him.
To safety.
[quietly]
Something's off about this, Ciri.
- The waters there were...
- Yes, they've worn off,
which means I'm thinking straight.
Do you know what happens to people
who escape a siege?
Because they don't just vanish.
They get captured and they get turned.
Remember what the Dryad Queen said.
- "Ask the right questions."
- [Mousesack sighs]
It's not just your life, Ciri.
It's mine too.
[clinking]
[Mousesack] Princess, I forgot.
I brought this for you.
My grandmother's sash.
[gasps]
[birds chirping]
Has anyone seen my escort?
[Yarpen] Ah! Bloody ball sacks!
Who slits a man's throat
while he's relieving his bowels?
Is nothing sacred anymore?
Ugh.
Fuck!
[Véa] We're halfway to the dragon's lair,
but it's getting dangerous.
- We cannot continue like this.
- [Yarpen] The warrior woman is right.
Someone killed that self-righteous fud,
and it wasn't any of us.
Somebody's not playin' fair.
Our people used to mine these mountains.
We know a shortcut
that will cut half a day off our journey.
Let the Reavers take the long way around.
We'll nab the treasure
before they even set foot in the cave.
We'll watch each other's backs
until we reach the next peak,
then every man for himself.
- What say ye?
- Let's go.
Aah!
Go on. I'll catch up.
Did you kill Eyck?
Kill him?
That's rather pedestrian.
And you're the one who's been
staring daggers at him since we arrived.
It was the Reavers.
That bastard Boholt killed my escort
before he could accomplish the one
damn task I actually needed him for.
And what was that?
Yen!
What are you really doing here?
I'm here for the dragon.
There are certain healing properties
it's rumored to possess.
I thought your transformation
healed all parts of you?
At the cost of losing others, yes.
Yennefer...
do not tell me
you've traveled all this way
for made-up fertility cures
using fresh dragon hearts?
- They're not made up!
- They are.
And seriously?
You, a mother?
Do you think I'd make a bad one?
Definitely.
Yen...
A child? What could you possibly want
with a child?
They took my choice. I want it back.
Not that I'd expect you to understand.
I didn't choose to become a witcher.
[sighs] Listen...
the people who made us,
they made us sterile for a lot of reasons.
One of the kinder ones
is because this lifestyle isn't suited
to a child.
What?
You were going to summon chaos
on kings' orders
in between feeding and naps?
- Do not patronize me!
- I'm not.
I've thought about this. Often.
And I'd rather use
my Child Surprise as bruxa bait
than subject it to this life!
What did you just say?
Uh...
Ah, fuck!
You have a Child Surprise?
[laughs]
Isn't that rich?
You lecture me on made-up cures
for having a child,
meanwhile you cheat with destiny
to steal one.
Every time I'm near you,
I say more in five minutes
than I've said in weeks.
And I always regret it.
[sighs]
The dwarfs,
they're leading us to a shorter path.
Come along.
I can take care of myself.
You don't always have to.
Come with me.
He's waiting for us.
Did you ever stop missing Skellige?
What?
It's just that I don't think
I'll ever stop missing Cintra, but...
you left your home to come raise me,
how did you feel about that?
I was...
very homesick.
Remember when we'd visit?
Ice skating with Crach an Craite?
He always said he let me win,
but I was just faster.
- Did you miss the cold too?
- Yes, very much.
- Except you have arthritis!
- [sighs]
You hate the cold!
And you always said Skellige
was where you came from
but Cintra was your home, with us!
- Hey!
- I've had enough of you.
- Mousesack, stop!
- Our name is not Mousesack!
We killed Mousesack
- and took his disgusting form...
- [gasps]
- ...to find you.
- [yells]
[groans]
- [sizzling]
- [Doppler yells]
[grunting]
We prefer it like this anyway.
[yells]
[groaning]
[rumbling]
[grunting]
[snarls]
[yelling]
Where are you taking us?
Who wants her?
- The man with the winged helmet.
- Why is he going to so much trouble?
I'm special. I don't know how or why,
but there's something inside me.
- Kill him!
- What?
Then I'll do it!
Wait, no, no, no, no, no!
[snarling]
[yells]
[Yarpen]
Mind the scree fallin', hear me?
Can get a bit rocky round here
if it's windy.
Which...
it is.
[wind whistling]
We're here.
Yeah, you're right, this is a shortcut...
to death.
You wanna beat those Reavers or not?
- We should turn back.
- No.
- We're very close.
- How can you possibly know that?
'Tis a perfectly fine route.
- For a dwarf.
- Aah!
Stifle your mewlin'. You'll manage.
As long as you don't look down.
- [groans]
- [laughs]
[sighs]
- [Yarpen] See ya on the other side!
- [Jaskier] Yeah, yeah, yes.
- Uh...
- [Yarpen shouts]
Uh, ladies first?
Ah! All right. Yep.
Come on, Jask. You've got this.
- You've got this.
- [Yarpen] Come on!
[Yennefer grunts]
[Yarpen] Careful!
Oh, whoa!
Oh, fuck! Oh...
Oh, that is not a good sign.
That is not a good sign.
[Yarpen shouts]
[wood creaking]
[Jaskier] Phew!
[creaking]
- [Véa screams]
- [Borch groans]
- [yells]
- [Geralt] Okay...
- [gasps]
- [strains]
- Geralt!
- Get back!
Sir Witcher, you will save us yet.
But first, you must let go.
No.
[creaking]
- [grunts]
- [Yennefer gasps]
- Geralt! The planks won't hold!
- [panting]
Thank you.
[grunts] No!
[gasps]
[Jaskier] You did your best.
There's nothing else you could have done.
[wind whistling]
Look, why don't we leave tomorrow?
That is, if you'll give me another chance
to prove myself a...
worthy travel companion.
[Geralt] Hm.
We could head to the coast.
Get away for a while.
Sounds like something Borch would say,
doesn't it?
Life is too short.
Do what pleases you...
while you can.
[Geralt] Composing your next song?
[Jaskier] No, I'm just, uh...
Just trying to work out what pleases me.
[sighs]
Hm.
So simple.
- Do you like it?
- [sighs]
[sighs]
Is this not what you came for?
I came for you.
I was afraid
that mountain would take you from me,
but now I fear
it took your senses instead.
Only my nonsense.
I quite like your nonsense.
[sighing] Hm...
That scent.
The moment I dread most
every time you leave...
is when it fades.
[sighs]
When you're really gone.
You left first.
In Rinde.
I woke up in that destroyed house
and you were gone.
Forgive me.
Do you hurt?
I don't mean physical pain.
They say
witchers can't feel human emotion.
They say whatever justifies
despising our kind.
Huh.
Do you regret it?
Becoming a witcher?
[sighs]
It's hard to regret something
you didn't choose.
But if the choice had been yours,
what would you have done instead?
A farmer?
A stableman?
[both chuckle]
- Horses are good company.
- [laughs]
But if I ever dreamed
of being something...
other... than what I am...
it was too long ago to remember.
Did you dream of being a mage?
I didn't have much of a choice either.
[sighs]
Did you always want to become a mother?
I dreamed...
of becoming important to someone.
Someday.
Hm.
Do I bore you?
[chuckles] Not at all.
[laughs]
Before we met,
the days were calm...
and the nights were restless.
But now... [sighs]
you're important to me.
Good morning.
Hm.
- [bird calling]
- [wind whistling]
At a quick pace, we can make it back
to the Pensive Dragon before sundown.
What are you talking about?
We're almost at the top.
I came here for a reason, Geralt.
I'm not leaving
till I've killed that dragon.
Yen, no!
- What will it solve?
- It will solve everything.
Wait.
Where are those fucking dwarfs?
Yen!
[yelps]
[whimpers]
[breathing shakily]
Don't scream.
I understand why you're afraid.
If there had been any other way
to extract you, I'd have done it.
It was never my intention
to torment you, Princess.
All I want...
all I've ever wanted is
to help you fulfill your destiny.
The White Flame has brought us together.
You are the key to everything, Cirilla.
You must be starving.
I'll get you something to eat.
[crackling]
[rumbling]
What have you done?
You lied to us.
You didn't tell us what she is.
What she's capable of.
You fucking fool!
[grunting]
[panting] Uh-uh!
We know all your tricks.
[yells]
Do you really believe all this nonsense
in your head?
- This prophecy?
- [groans]
We think you're insane!
[yells]
[grunting]
[yelling]
[yells]
- [crunching]
- You are an abomination!
I will destroy you!
[both grunting]
[yells]
[screams]
[grunting]
You're still here, aren't you?
[scree tumbling]
[Yennefer speaks Elder]
[panting]
[shuddering]
[gasps]
No closer!
What the fuck?
Get back!
You should've stayed dead.
[Geralt] Stop!
How?
He's dead.
She's dead.
[roaring]
[roars]
[Borch] Sir Witcher and his sorceress.
[low growl]
Hello again.
Impossible.
[Téa] When the dragoness was injured,
her cry was heard by Villentretenmerth.
But the egg could not be moved
or the life inside it would die.
That's why the dragon attacked.
[heart beating]
She was protecting her baby.
[Téa] And then we heard
about the King's hunt,
realized we had to keep our enemies close.
So I came to find you,
the white-haired witcher,
the knight who was taught
to save dragons instead of kill them.
[growling]
Looks like
we get to fuck up the whole family.
Slay that dragon!
[Geralt yells]
Kill them!
Boholt's mine!
Aard, now!
[yelling]
[low growl]
[Borch] I'm afraid we have more.
Go! I'll protect the egg.
Get them!
- [Yennefer yells]
- [grunts]
[Yennefer yells]
So I get to kill you after all, Witcher.
[yells]
[roaring]
It's not going to happen!
Shame you don't get to see me
crack that egg!
[groans]
[both panting]
[gasps]
Uh...
[sniffs]
Geralt?
Dwarfs?
Oh, gosh. Phew!
Ah! What'd I miss?
Huh?
- Guys?
- [groaning]
Are we... queuing for something?
- What's going on?
- [gasping]
Oh, no!
Oh, fuck!
What happened?
Oh, gosh!
Oh! Bloody hell.
What the fuck are you doing here?
Well, that's fuckin' shite!
We missed a whole mother lode of fun.
Ask no questions, and in return,
I offer you these to take to the King.
Dragon teeth?
I've never been one
to look a gift cock in the beak,
though this might not be enough proof
to collect the reward.
Tell the King if he's not satisfied,
he can expect the body of a dragon
dropped upon his royal wedding.
Free of charge.
[laughing]
Aah!
[whimpering]
[twigs snapping]
[footsteps approaching]
[whimpers]
[muffled cries]
He caught me. He's going to come back,
Dara. We have to hurry.
[Dara curses in Elder]
If we had just stayed in Brokilon, Ciri,
we'd be safe right now!
- How could I have known?
- Because we agreed to it. Hmm?
If I stay with you any longer,
I'll be dead too.
And you say you're so special.
What you really mean is
that you're just like Calanthe!
You bring terror and you bring death
wherever you are!
I'm doing the best that I can.
I'm done apologizing.
I'm done with all of this.
I have to move on.
You're right, Princess.
Find a new family,
because I can't be there for you anymore.
This is my final first.
A child.
This treasure, this legacy
must endure.
There is no other reason to go on.
Thank you for protecting it.
And thank you, Yennefer of Vengerberg.
I can see why Geralt didn't want
to lose you.
What does that mean?
In Rinde.
The djinn.
That's why we can't escape each other.
Why I feel this way inside.
No.
[Yennefer]
It's not because of anything real...
or true.
You made a wish.
It's magic.
- It's real, Yen.
- How could we ever know?
Disregard for other's freedom
has become quite your trademark.
- I made that wish to save your life.
- I didn't need your help!
Like fuck you didn't!
And you, you flit about like a tornado,
wreaking havoc, and for what?
So you can have a baby?
A child is no way
to boost your fragile ego, Yen.
I'll take advice from you about children
as soon as you take responsibility
for the one you bound to you
and then abandoned!
[Borch] That's enough.
I'm going to save you both a lot of hurt
with a little pain now.
The sorceress will never regain her womb.
And though you didn't want to lose her,
Geralt,
you will.
He already has.
You wanted to show me
what I was missing...
there she goes.
What you're missing is still out there.
Your legacy.
Your destiny. I know it.
And you know it.
[Jaskier] Phew! What a day! [chuckles]
- I imagine you're probably...
- Damn it, Jaskier!
Why is it whenever I find myself
in a pile of shit these days,
- it's you, shoveling it?
- Well, that's not fair.
The Child Surprise, the djinn,
all of it!
If life could give me one blessing,
it would be to take you off my hands.
Right. Uh...
Right, then.
I'll...
I'll go get the rest of the story
from the others.
See you around, Geralt.
[Cahir winces]
[Fringilla]
They're combing the area.
They haven't found him,
or the girl.
A simple test of silver would've sufficed.
I had steel at the ready.
We can pull in more soldiers.
Keep searching.
We won't stop.
We cannot mistake the stars reflecting
in a pond for those in the night sky.
Spare me the lecture, Fringilla.
You rose up against the Usurper.
Helped free our people from their chains.
I witnessed the White Flame call on you...
mold you...
anoint you.
It burns in you, Cahir.
She is the key,
but you...
you are the commissioner.
Do not despair.
We will find her.
And we will spread his supremacy
all through the kingdoms,
whether they deserve it...
or not.
Gather the men.
We cannot fail him.
The time of the sword
and the ax is nigh.
[Jaskier] ♪ The "fairer sex"
They often call it ♪
♪ But her love's as unfair as a crook ♪
♪ It steals all my reason ♪
♪ Commits every treason ♪
♪ Of logic with naught but a look ♪
♪ A storm raging on the horizon ♪
♪ Of longing, and heartache, and lust ♪
♪ She's always bad news ♪
♪ It's always lose-lose ♪
♪ So, tell me, love, tell me, love
How is that just? ♪
♪ But the story is this ♪
♪ She'll destroy with her sweet kiss ♪
♪ Her sweet kiss ♪
♪ But the story is this ♪
♪ She'll destroy with her sweet kiss ♪
♪ Her current is pulling you closer ♪
♪ A charge in the hot, humid night ♪
♪ The red sky at dawn
Is giving a warning ♪
♪ You fool, better stay out of sight ♪
♪ I'm weak, my love, and I am wanting ♪
♪ If this is the path I must trudge ♪
♪ I'll welcome my sentence ♪
♪ Give to you my penance ♪
♪ Garroter, jury and judge ♪
♪ But the story is this ♪
♪ She'll destroy with her sweet kiss ♪
♪ Her sweet kiss, oh ♪
♪ But the story is this ♪
♪ She'll destroy with her sweet kiss ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ But the story is this ♪
♪ She'll destroy with her sweet kiss ♪
♪ Her sweet kiss, oh ♪
♪ But the story is this ♪
♪ She'll destroy with her sweet kiss ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ The story is this ♪
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org